Thank you for watching!
Nogizaka Morning
Nogizaka Let's Sing!
A team singing competition between Nogizaka and Bananaman.
The second half of the karaoke showdown, where if you answer the intro quiz correctly, you score points by singing only the chorus of that song.
So far, the red team is leading the battle by a wide margin to second place or two!
Let's see which team will win the karaoke duel!
Let's Go! Let's Sing Nogizaka!
Let's go! Let's sing Nogizaka!
Okay, okay.
It's blue.
It sounded like an explosion.
What's the name of the song?
I think I got the name of the song.
Blue.
I'll say it.
Say it.
Okay, here we go.
Grown-up Blue.
Wow!
Adult Blue.
The new school leaders.
Well, that's a relief.
Blue team got the intro right.
Thank you for watching!
I don't know how you got it out after all that hesitation.
That's great!
Blue team got 88 points here!
In addition, the blue team got 88 points.
I really don't get it. I really don't know.
What was it?
YESTERDAY by Official Beard Dandyism.
I made a mistake.
I couldn't get it.
Ehhhh...
Red got it.
We thought for sure we'd get it, too.
Here comes Red!
Official Mustache Dandyism's NO DOUBT!
I made a mistake.
Yay!
I'm Noricum!
Future Map 2
Yay!
Wow, you sing this?
Bananaman's team, whose karaoke privileges have so far failed to improve.
Kimura took up the challenge!
Himura stumbled at the beginning, but what was his solution?
Entering the lottery
Result mode
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I got it.
There you go.
There we go.
Here we go.
Oh, there it goes. There it goes.
Oh, it's okay. It's okay.Oh, okay, okay.
Why don't you go to this one?
Hey, I'm not coming back to this place.
Why? 80!
Don't fuck with me!
Why not?
We're not getting in, are we?
I don't know... you were in here earlier.
What? He said...
That's a tinkle.
That's a cramp.
That's a trowel.
Okay, let's go.
Here we go.
Ready?
Let's sing Nogizaka!
Let's go, blue team!
Here you go.
Tamamizuki
Come on, how did you get there?
Correct!
You got me.
Oh, that was so good!
Shibata of the blue team had his first karaoke here!
How good is he?
I knew it!
I knew it.as I thought
I knew it. I knew it.
I knew it!
Thank you for your hard work.
You know, Nogizaka is a good singer, right?
I know, I know.
I've never heard each one sing so differently.
Shibata's good.
Nice job, Shibata!
They're all the same.
Here we go.
I think it's high.
Yay!
High, high, high!
I got the highest score. 96.403.
I love it.
How did he get 10 points higher than us?
Oh, my God.
We're coming up on blue.Blue is pretty close.
Don't put the blue on.
I'll put the blue on.
Here we go.
Let's sing "Nogizaka.
Blue!
It's blue!
A cat.
A cat?
I know cats.
Oh, my God!
I'm a cat.
I've become a cat!
Blue team got it right and it's Umezawa who sings!
Thank you for watching!
The blue team is in the mood to catch up with the blue team with 84 points!
Let's go!
Ultraman Town!
What?
What's that? Sorry, you said that!
You've heard it before, right?
You guys don't get it, so I'm going to ask you one more time. Se-no.
Nogizaka, let's sing!
Let's sing it, Nogizaka!
I remember this song.
I knew this one.
I knew it, but it didn't come out
Naked Heart
That's right.
That's right. Correct.
I see... that's a start.
that's right
I got it!
Shakurin Yukichi is back with Aimyon!
That's good. It's so good!
Iyoki Have you sung this one before? Yes, I have!
It's good, isn't it?
Shakurin no yuki scored an impressive 88 points!
Up to this point, the red team was in the lead, but from this point on, there was a new rule.
Once out of three times, a new system was added whereby a team could take over the karaoke score from a team of its choice.
After this, it became a super heated battle for the championship!
The red team will be targeted.
The red team will have to be more on their own, especially with the problems there.
Yellow is just the opposite.
But on the other hand, we can crush the red team as well.
We're going to do our best.
We're going to go for it right now, and we're going to take it from them.
I'd like to take this one.
Let's do it!
Nogizaka!
Oh, there it is!
Let's go, red team!
Give me a bouquet of flowers with all your love
Strong!
Red team
This is the one that can't be done by the red team
This is the one that Okada really has to work hard for.
That's right.
The red team has a chance to take it sideways and widen the gap quickly. Red Teams Can Make a Quick Difference with a Chance to Take it Lateral
Red Teams Can Make a Quick Gap with a Chance to Take it Lateral
Will the red team widen the gap at once with a chance to take it sideways?
Will the red team widen the gap with a chance to take it sideways?
The red team is good and can take this score from somewhere.
So which team will the red team take points from?
Let's see!
Bananaman!
The team in second place here is Bananaman, and they're going to take it from them.
Will they continue to run alone?
Perfect Friends
Bananaman again won the usual question with no greed, and
Sarang did it!
Ai no ue no ue nakatta kasei no yamakuni no tenshi ga tei
Bananaman added another 85 points for consecutive correct answers Yama san is on the stage because he's a person
I'm out as a person
ah ah ah ah, and again a chance to take it sideways
Wait a minute
No way!
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I totally get it.
Ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten.
Mr. Himura.
Oh, Mr. Himura.
Get wild!
OK!
Yeah!Yay!
Bananaman in intro muso state
Nimura aims for high score in OHACO's Get Wild
Bananaman in get-wild state
Bananaman aims for a high score in Get Wild
Bananaman of Get Wild
Bananaman aims for a high score with Get Wild
Why is there no shaku-uri at all?
He's not scooting.
Why isn't he shaku shaku?
How do you not get the shaku-uri?
What's wrong? Not enough shakuri?
The score didn't go up.
It's yoko-chiri.
I don't want to get caught in the middle anymore.
Let's start with the yellow.
Please don't do that.
We'll lose all heart!
Of course, Bananaman will take the points from the red team.
They're in first place now!
Bananaman has equaled the score for the third consecutive time, and the battle for the top is very crowded!
And again, the usual question
[Correct answer
Wow!
What's this?
Ayaka's crescent moon.
Wow, amazing!
Yes!
[correct sound]
Why are you singing along and getting all excited?Why are you singing along and getting all excited?
Oh no!
Each punk got a high score, defeating the obstruction of the uncle who sings along.
However, the next question was again answered correctly by Bananaman!
And again, a chance to take the side that you really want to take!
I'm sure everyone understood this one.
Sailor Legend.
No, it's not.
Ugh, yellow.
The Legend of Moonlight.
It's been a while since we've had an intro, so let's see where the yellow team takes the score.
Well, it's a toss-up, so let's see if the yellow team takes it from the red team.
Yay!
Customized from the red team with a nail clock!
We're going to try to get back on track from here.
But after this, the usual problem is bananama
And the blue team adds a point
Now we have a side-taking problem.
No, Red and us have to defend here, or they'll take it here.
But Blue, on the other hand, if they get it here, it's pretty big.
Let's go, let's go!
Nogizaka!
Oh, they've got the red one...
I'd like to hear a little more.
I'd like to hear a little more about this.
Here you go!
Masaki Sudasaki's Niji
Wow!
Congratulations! Congrats!!!
Strong! That's strong!
Yumiki, with his intro in great form, goes straight into the karaoke challenge!
Here, the red team has a chance to get 88 points!
Which team will take it?
Seino
Bananaman!
The red team and Bananaman are very much competing with each other!
It's a heated battle for the top spot.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Let's go!
Sanaka Nogi, Utoh!
Ah!
Red again! I got red!
Snow Flower
Wow, I was right!
Snowflake.
Snowflakes!
Snowflake
Snowflakes
Oh, my God.
You're good!
Okuda scored a high 93 points.
Oh, no!
Another red runner-up.
Let's stop it.
Let's go.
Ready, Nogizaka? Yarrow!Seino Nogizaka Yaro
Here you go... dried flowers in blue.
Dried flowers were a big hit about 2 years ago, right?
Yuri.
Yuri Saito.
No, it's not.
Umezawa takes on senior Yuri's song.
Umezawa takes on Yuri's song
Umezawa Challenges to the Song of Yuri, a Major Senior
Umezawa challenges Yuri's song
And there it was
Yay!
The score was 91 points!
The blue team is still aiming for the top!
And the remaining 5 questions were all participated
And there's more.
There are five more questions left.
They're all up for grabs.
Whoo-hoo!
Let's flip it over.
Five questions later.
We're really going to turn it all over.
All right, let's do it.
Nogizawa, let's sing!
There you go.
Marigold.
Marigold!
We did it!
Bananaman won! Ready, Bananaman! Bananaman won! Ready, Bananaman!
All right!
I can't get out at all!
Bananaman won the first all-or-nothing question!
Don't worry, I gave him a "hey".
Hey, I gave it to you.
I have the same hair as Ebi Kimura.
I'm faster than you.
I can do it!
Ebi Kimura!
Kimura's first 90.5 of the day.
Yay!
We'll take it from the red team.
Four more to go.
Cherry!
We did it!
You're so strong.
Cherry is spit, right?
Yui's.
Yui's? Then I don't know.
Cherry is...
I've done this before... with a guitar.
You've done it... with a guitar.
Iwamoto matches her high score with her debut song
Bananaman doubles his score again.
Here we go. Let's go.
Let's sing "No-gi-saka" (Let's sing "No-gi-saka")
Wow, so fast!
Beautiful fins!
No, it's not.
Come on, blue
Mr. Spitz's cherry
Wow.
We've got a cherry connection.
Wow, you're right.
The blue team took the trick cherry.
Tsutsui takes the challenge!
The blue team that took the blue team's cherry
The blue team took the blue team's cherry
The blue team that took the blue team's cherry was
Huwei, who just figured it out... in the end.
Wow, Numé, you're good.
Now where did you get this from?
And the blue team takes the red team's 88.
Do we still have a song called "Cherry?
Maybe not cherry.
Cherry Cherry Cherry!
We're down to our last two songs.
I'll triple your score if you get just one color.
No, I'm serious.
Now, any team can win.
Who will win the next round?
Nogizaka Unao
I got blue.
Why are you pushing blue?Why are you pressing blue?
Seino
I like it so much I feel stupid.
You're right.
Got it!
Koeda Amagi
Correct!
This is
No, no, no, you say this kind of thing every time.
You're right.
The winner is over Nogizaka! Shimoda sings a classic!
Buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh...
I'm not going... it won't go over at all.
What do you mean, Technique Man?
Bananaman again crosses the score from the red team... and the final question.
here we go... the last one!
Nogizaka udon
Oh, wow!
Here we go, blue.
Ready?
New era, new era
Oh, I've been pushed down.
We're down.
Come on, red team on.
Ready, set, go!
Ultrasoul
That's right.
This is worse than I knew.
They took it. Taken.
The red team wins the last game, and it's Lidiana Ito playing Ootori.
Now, the red team plays Ito, Lidiana, Otori.
Now, the red team plays the grand tori of Lidiana Ito.
And now, red team, Ito and Lidiana play the grand tori.
Yay!
Yeah! Yeah!
Ah-chan, strong!
And the winner of the shining 86 points is...
Mr. Bananaman!
Did the final takedown move the standings?
The results of the hotly contested Nogizaka Uta Oto are in!
First, from 4th place with 271.979 points
The yellow team
The yellow team was a little bit of a surprise.
And then the 3rd place
Third place, with 724 points, 556!
Which team came in third?
Red team!
Oh, my God!
You guys were too strong!
It's either Ao or Buo or us!
Third place went to the red team!
I thought I was going to jump out of my skirt in third place.
Yay!
Guess what everyone predicted.
No way!
Ao took off the red one.
Please.
Which one of you won the first Pig-O?Who won the first Pig-O?
The winning team was
Ao.
Wow, they crushed each other.
Seriously.
So Red and we crushed each other?
I knew it.
We did it.
I can't do it if I fly away from Ao at the end.
It'll go something like this.
Oh, man, that's good.
I didn't give up already.
I was kinda thinking.
We're fighting for it here.
I'm pretty sure they're not gonna take this place.
Here you go.
And the second prize, the Ao team.
Wow.
That's huge.
Big!
Yum!
It's so big!
It's a little bit... nice and flat.
How did we lose?
That time in Ultra Soul...
Oh, my God, it's gone.
The moment we all said "Ultrasoul
It was a winning Ultrasoul.
You thought it was WinningYou thought it was a win-win.
When we stopped at Ultra Soul just for fun.
I was totally tired.
I wish you would turn it off.
I'm Aya Ogawa.
Kaede-san followed me.
Since you followed me so closely.
I'd like to imitate a cat.
Miao.
What do you think?
If you like it, please subscribe to my channel.